{
    "subject": "resource/Charles_Grene_Ellicombe",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/surname",
    "object": "Ellicombe",
    "human_readable": "The surname of Charles Grene Ellicombe is Ellicombe.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9884501695632935,
            "question": "Is 'Ellicombe' the surname of Charles Grene Ellicombe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9867140650749207,
            "question": "What is the surname of Charles Grene Ellicombe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9368496537208557,
            "question": "What is Charles Grene Ellicombe's last name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9282950758934021,
            "question": "How would you write Charles Grene Ellicombe's surname?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9194169640541077,
            "question": "What is the family name of Charles Grene Ellicombe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8420020341873169,
            "question": "If you were writing a letter addressed to Charles Grene Ellicombe, what name would you use after his given names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8204229474067688,
            "question": "Which part of Charles Grene Ellicombe's full name identifies his family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8013166785240173,
            "question": "What is the final element of Charles Grene Ellicombe's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7808743119239807,
            "question": "What is the name that would be passed down through generations in Charles Grene Ellicombe's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7748745083808899,
            "question": "If Charles Grene Ellicombe was listed in a phone book, what name would appear?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The surname of Charles Grene Ellicombe is Ellicombe.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2259_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name that would be passed down through generations in Charles Grene Ellicombe's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2259_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the final element of Charles Grene Ellicombe's full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2259_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which part of Charles Grene Ellicombe's full name identifies his family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2259_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2259_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2259_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2259_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2259_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2259_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2259_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2259_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2259_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2259_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2259_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because the documents mention \"Sir Charles Grene Ellicombe (1783-1871), British general, Royal Engineers, son of the Rev. William Ellicombe\", and it explicitly states that his surname is indeed \"Ellicombe\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe context information mentions Sir Charles Grene Ellicombe and provides his family name as Ellicombe, supporting the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}